would like to take your view on some other segments. Insurance is a segment of financials,
it hasn't taken off at all. There was a
lot of promise in it, people,
funds and investors bought it, but
unfortunately, it has underperformed. Now,
some steps are being taken by IRDA
which will implement new reforms. If
you like some segment in the insurance space, will
you get advice on it somewhere?
Look, life insurance
companies have a lot of potential, but
you saw the valuation issue that came up within it.
Almost all the partners of these companies have offloaded a large part of their share
holdings.
So, the biggest problem that has arisen in this market,
apart from earnings, is that there is so much
supply of this paper in the market
because all the partners have started offloading the
shares. So, the situation that has arisen now is
that domestic investors are sitting on this stock.
These companies have a long gestation period. There is no problem in the company,
but the problem is that it will take a
lot of time for you to get returns.  And this is
typically the stock of institutional shareholders, not just globally in India, but
globally as well,
where they have the capacity to
hold for 8 years or 10 years, where
they need an average rate of return of 7 to 8 years, that is fine
in India, that investor is fine,
your problem in India is that our
opportunity cost is at 17-18, it will be very difficult for you to
earn returns at 17-18 from the insurance company,
considering two things, the
foreign investors who were partners have
sold out, secondly, whatever you may
say is the growth rate of India, your
income will increase as per that and insurance will increase,
apart from that, it
is very difficult to get a return of 18, forget it, so
many IPOs are happening for institutions, so many
new companies are coming,
now you should look for new themes,
what do you have to do with the old themes in the market